Inventory of the Broadside Case Collection, 1896 - 2004
Broadside Case Collection, 1896 - 2004
- Posters, 1968-1998
  - Davison Art Center Events, 1970-1987 (Folder 2)
    - Amy Vandersall. The Archer on the Franks Casket: The Survival of Homeric Myth in Early Medieval England. Davison Art Center. March 1, year unknown.
    - Otto von Simson. Gothic Illusionism: The Sainte-Chapelle. Davison Art Center. Apr 19, No Year.
    - Jacqueline Gourevitch. Cloud Paintings 1964- 1971. Davison Art Center. Oct 8-24, year unknown. (3 copies)
    - The Seat of American Invention. Davison Art Center. Mar 17 - Apr 10, 1972.
    - Prints and Drawings by Gabriel de Saint-Aubin 1724-1780. Davison Art Center. Mar 8 - Apr 13, 1975.
    - Harry Callahan. Davison Art Center. Oct 11- 26, 1977.
    - Images of Death. Davison Art Center. January 25- Mar 2, 1975. (2 copies)
    - Glitter! A Brilliant Costume Ball, Friends of DAC, April 7, circa 1970s
    - Robert F. Sheehan: Color Photography, 1948-1958. Davison Art Center. September 2-October 28, 1987.
  - Events Posters, 1960s-1990s (Folder 3-4)
    - Wesleyan Photographs: Philip Trager, Wesleyan Sesquicentennial, 1831-1981. Wesleyan University Press.
    - What's Wrong with Fighting for a Lesbian/Gay Rights Bill. A Talk by Henry Abelove. April 17, PAC. ca. 1986.
    - What's Wrong with Fighting for a Lesbian/Gay Rights Bill. A Talk by Henry Abelove. April 17, PAC. ca. 1986.
    - Gay Politics. Handwritten poster, ca. 1986.
    - Artstop 1986 - Celebrate Summer, CFA.
    - The Winter's Tale, Directed by Daphne Levens, CFA, August, ca. 1980s
    - Scenes of the Wesleyan Campus, 1996.
    - Gaia and the Microcosm. Lynn Margulis. 150 Science Center. Oct 3 1990.
    - The Einstein Years. Cultural History and Public Affairs. Science Center. Oct 15-26, 1979. Sponsored by the Wesleyan University Public Affairs Center with support from the Connecticut Humanities Council.
    - Ralph Nader. The Chapel. Nov 17 1969. Sponsored by the Student Events Committee.
    - Ralph Nader. The Chapel. Nov 17 1969. Sponsored by the Student Events Committee.
    - The Seventeenth Annual Beta Symposium. Evolution - Revolution: The American University. Speakers Norman Rudich, Eugene Golob, Joseph McMahon, and Robert Fuller. Sponsored by Beta Theta Pi. C.S.S. Lounge. Nov 13 - 14, 1968
    - Roleno Adorno. The Spanish New World in the American Narrative Imagination. Sponsored by Wesleyan's Center for the Americas. Russell House. April 23 1998.
    - Black Gothic. Gender Relations to Race and Class in Post-Colonial America. Led by Carol Smith-Rosenberg. Sponsored by Wesleyan's Center for the Americas. Russell House. April 30, 1998.
    - A Joyce Vaudeville. Odds and Ends from Finnegans Wake. Sponsored by the Center for the Humanities. Russell House. February 1 1982.
    - The Black Image: Illusion and Reality. Lecture Series, Center for Afro-American Studies. Marcus Garvey Lounge, Center fro Afro-American Studies. September 28 - November 30, 1982
    - Elia Kazan / A Retrospective. Presented by the Wesleyan film program on the occasion of the inauguration of the Cinema of the CFA. September 16-29.
    - A tribute to Miss Joan Crawford. Sponsored by The Student Committee of Wesleyan. McConaughy Hall. November 29, 1972.
    - Films, May 15 By Wesleyan Filmmakers. Includes Plastage, The Shot, Waterfall, The Sunday the Kids and I went to Wadsworth, and Blue Skies. May 15, 1968, Shanklin.
    - A New England Sacred Harp Singing. Led by Hugh Mcgraw. October 2, 1976. Wesleyan University Chapel.
    - Patterns in Science--Time for Change. Lord Alexander Todd. October 22. Science Center 150.
    - Inauguration Concert. Wesleyan University Music Dept. October 20, 1967.
    - Three Films by Wesleyan Filmmakers: Beyond the Wizard of Oz, The Ruthyn Curse, and Awakening. Feb. 14, Science Tower 150.
    - An Evening with Wilbert Snow. Wednesday, February 12 in the Jones Room. Theater Studios.
    - The Baccalaureate Service: Wesleyan University's One Hundred and Thirty-Sixth Commencement. Memorial Chapel. June 9, 1968.
    - Wesleyan Football, 1972. Schedule of Games for the '72 season.
    - Philip Trager. Photographs of Architecture. Wesleyan University Press.
    - Mysticism and the Occult. Spanish House Symposium. Emery Fletcher-March 13; Heinrich Schwarz-March 19; Stephen D. Crites-April 4. Jeremy Zwelling-April 9; James H. Helfer- April 16. Spanish House, 1968.
    - Wesleyan University Press 25th Anniversary Convocation. The Scholarly Publishing of Controversial Books. April 23rd, Russell House. No year.
    - Women of the World War I Poster. Care for Her Through the YWCA. For Every Fighter a Woman Worker. Center for the Arts Gallery. 28, January-24 February, 1982.
    - Hollywood Portrait Photographers:1921-1941. Center for the Arts, South Gallery 3--27 November, 1980.
    - John Cage at Wesleyan. Feb. 22-27, no year. Crowell Concert Hall.
    - Disorientation. Deadline August 26, 2nd Floor of the Housing Office.
    - Forty Miles from Tokyo. Jokes for Credit-comedy. The Breakers-rock and roll. 92 Theater, August 8.
    - Middletown known originally as Mattabeseck... Sponsored by Middlesex Mutual Insurance Company, 1986.
    - John Wesley Iconography. Olin Library. November 3-December 31, 1981
    - There's more in the Middle, illustrated map of Middletown.
    - Hitchcock and Bergman. Presented by Alpha Delta Phi Assembly series and the Wesleyan Film Series. Sunday Feb 22 and Tues Feb 24, year unknown
    - Karl Kraus. Austrian Satirist- an exhibition of magazines, first editions, and other materials from the collection of Leo A. Lensing. November 10-26 1986.
    - Top of the Lizst. Produced by Sandra Schuldmann on behalf of the piano community. Honors college. December 12, 1986.
    - Auditions for choral singers. Wesleyan University concert choir, women's chorus. Directed by Robert Ford. January 21 and 22, 1287. (Duplicate poster)
    - Folk and art songs of the Jewish people. Leon Lishner and Melvin Strauss. Russell House. May 4, 1986.
    - New Talking Drums. A performance of West African Music and Dance, a highlife dance party. McConaughy Hall. November 7, 1987.
    - Mostly Madrigals. Works by Lasso, Sullivan, Berger, Rutter, Outwin, Gershwin. MPR Campus center.
    - Kafka's Clothes. Presentation by Mark Anderson, Columbia University. Honors College, Russell House. April 16 1987.
    - Pilgrimage. Outer journey, inner goal. Graduate liberal studies program. September 7 - December 17, 1987.
    - Colloquium on African Art. Rene A bravmann and Peter Mark. Sponsored by the art department and religion and African studies. Oct 6, 1987.
    - Memories of a Literary Marriage: Calligraphy, Photography, and First editions of Tanizaki Jun'ichiro and Matsuko. From the collection of Anthony H. Chambers. Mansfield Freeman Center for East Asian Studies Gallery. November 23 - December 11, 1987.
    - West African Music and Dance. Performed by Freeman Donkor and his Students. CFA Courtyard. May 8, 1987.
    - Richard Meier. A portrait of the architect in mid-career. CFA Cinema. April 30, 1987.
    - The Ebony Singers. Memorial Chapel. May 4 1987.
    - Candlelight concert. Wesleyan Concert Choir. Memorial Chapel. December 6 1987.
    - Organ Recital. James Dalton. Memorial Chapel. Oct 7, 1987.
    - French Christmas Music. The Wesleyan Singers. Memorial Chapel. Dec 8 1985.
    - Organ Recital. Charles Krigmaum. Memorial Chapel. Dec 11 1985.
    - Rosalind Krauss: Visual Arts Forum. CFA cinema. April 23 1987.
    - Wesleyan Student Filmmakers. CFA Cinema. May 10 1987.
    - Hepburn's favorite Hepburns. CFA Cinema. June 30-Aug 5, 1986.
    - Roy Strickland. Visual Arts Forum. CFA Cinema. Oct 23, 1986.
    - Jerry Uelsmann. Visual Arts Forum. CFA Cinema. Oct 9, 1986.
    - Student Films and Videos of 1986. CFA Cinema. May 10 - 11, 1986. (Triplicate poster)
    - James McGarrel. Visual Arts Forum. CFA Cinema. Feb 19 1986.
    - Yvonne Jacquette. Visual Arts Forum. CFA Cinema. Feb 5 1987
    - Visual Arts Forum 1986-1987. University art department. Oct 1986 - April 1987.
    - Roberta Smith. Visual Arts Forum. CFA Cinema. Nov 20 1986.
    - Italo Scanga. Visual Arts Forum. CFA Cinema. Oct 30, 1986.
    - Mark Hall Amitin. Theater in Contemporary China. CFA Cinema. Nov 24, 1986.
    - Holiday Concert: Ebony singers. Memorial Chapel. December 12, 1985.
    - Philip Prince: Organ Recital. Memorial Chapel. Oct 29, 1986.
    - The Wesleyan Singers. Directed by Robert Ford. Memorial Chapel. Nov 23, 1986.
    - The Ebony Singers. Spring Concert. Memorial Chapel. April 28 1986.
    - Organ Recital. James Welch. Memorial chapel. April 22 1986.
    - A Dripping Honeycomb. 12th-century songs for St. Ursula. Performed by Barbara Lachman Grant, Marie Nakouzi, Willa Needler, and Ellen Sweeny. Memorial Chapel. Feb 1, 1987.
    - Ebony singers. Holiday concert. Memorial Chapel. Dec 8 1986.
    - Candlelight Concert. The concert choir / the women's chorus. Memorial Chapel. December 7 1986.
    - Organ Recital. Ronald Elbrecht. Memorial Chapel. Nov 19 1986.
    - Organ Recital: Patricia Snyder. Memorial Chapel. Feb 18 1986.
  - Campus Events Posters (Folder 5)
    - John Cage at Wesleyan. CFA. Feb 22-27, 1988.
    - Art A la mode. Sponsored by the friends of the Davison Art center. Feb 9 and March 1, 1988.
    - Storytellers series. Sponsored by the Wesleyan theater department and the CFH. January 27 - February 18, 1988?
    - Nancy Armstrong. Evolving women: an uncanny history of the political unconsciousness. Russell House. Feb 15, 1988.
    - Larry Scanlon. Chaucer and Allegory: The politics of tradition. Russell house. Feb 8 1988.
    - Storytellers series. Robbie McCauley: My father and the Wars. World Music Hall CFA. Feb 10 1988.
    - Elizabeth Ewen and Rosalyn Baxandall. Picture windows: women in the Suburbs 1945 - present. Russell House. Feb 22, 1988.
    - Storytellers series. Paul Schmidt: Perfect Pleasures. World Music Hall. Feb 17, 1988
    - African American music in the Jazz Tradition. Crowell Concert Hall. February 12, 1988?
    - Kapelye. New York's Yiddish Klezmer Band. Crowell Concert Hall. Feb 14, 1988?
    - Storytellers series. I Nyoman Sumandhi. A Balinese shadow puppet play: Lelampahan Jaban Tatuka. And The performed word, A film by folklorist Gerald C. Davis. World Music Hall, CFA, and CFA Cinema. Jan 27 - 28, 1988.
    - Peter Hart, Singer. with Neely Bruce, piano. Crowell Concert Hall. Jan 22, 1988?
    - The Mitchell-Ruff duo. Crowell Concert Hall. January 29. 1988?
    - Dance: New Works. Lepkoff, Lourie, Martin, and Davidson. CFA Theater. Jan 22-23 1988?
    - Storytellers Series. Jan 27 - Feb 18 1988.
    - The Tempest. Directed by Daisy von Scherler Mayer. CFA Theater. Feb 11-13 1988.
    - J.W.B. vs. The Black Wholes. World Premier. A play by James Childs. '92 Theater. Feb 11-13 1988?.
    - Wesrevue. Crowell Concert hall. Feb 5 and 6, 1988
    - Postcard: Thomas McKnight. Paintings. Ezra & Cecile Zilkha Gallery. May 12-June 5, 1988
    - Gain Domenico Tiepolo and the Flight into Egypt. Davison Art Center. Jan 26-March 6, 1988
    - Modern Redux: Critical Alternatives for Architecture in the Next Decade. Ezra and Cecile Zilkha Gallery. Jan 20- Mar 6, 1988
    - Philip Johnson, Film Maker. Beyond Utopia. A film that is part of Modern Redux. Cinema. March 2, 1988?
    - Andrew Dolkart, Lecturer. Columbia: Paris/New York Program in Architecture and Preservation. CFA. March 1. Undated.
    - Charles Krigbaum. Organ Recital. Memorial Chapel. Jan 27. Undated.
    - Modern Chinese Painting from the Jeannette Shambaugh Elliot Collection. Mansfield Freeman Center for East Asian Studies Gallery. Mar 28 - May 6, 1988
    - Prints and Drawings From the Collection of Eileen and Gerald Burke. Davison Art Center. Mar 25 - May 8, 1988
    - Art A La Mode: Prints and Drawings From The Collection of Eileen and Gerald Burke. Speaker: Charles M. Young. Davison Art Center Gallery. April 12, no year. Complexity and Contradiction. Speaker: Klaus Ottmann. Ezra and Cecile Zilkha Gallery. May 10, no year.
    - Charles Swedlund. Recent Photographic Projects. Zilkha Gallery. April 28, no year
    - Ryan Alexander and Kara Stern. Senior Talks in the History of Art. Ryan Alexander: Twelfth-Century Mary Magdalene Iconography. Kara Stern: Hale Woodruff: An American Painter. Davison Art Center. April 21, n.d.
    - Kristen Jones. Installation Artists Jones & Ginzel: A Slide Talk by Kristen Jones. Zilkha Gallery. April 20, n.d.
    - Mansfield Freeman Center for East Asian Studies presents Lord of the Dance, Destroyer of Illusion: A film Unveiling the Beauty and Mystery of Tibetan Tantric Ritual From Inside a Buddhist Monastery in the Himalayas. 58 Science Center. April 20, 1988.
    - Patricia Brown, Princeton University. Measured Friendship, Calculated Pomp: The Ceremonial Welcomes of the Venetian Republic. 100 DAC. April 14, n.d.
    - Jill Johnston, lecturer. Jasper Johns: The Spy and the Watchman. CFA Cinema. April 7, n.d.
    - Lu Ying, Painter. Lecture/ Demonstration on Chinese Painting. 343 Washington Terrace. April 6, 1988.
    - Wesleyan University Center for Humanities. A Fiction Reading by Fred Pfeil, Rockefeller Fellow: Variations on Cold. The Center For Humanities Colloquium Room, 95 Pearl Street. Apr. 27, 1988.
    - Wesleyan University Center for Humanities. Film Screening: The Color Purple. 109 Science Center. Apr. 25, 1988. Hazel Carby, Faculty Fellow: Histories of Containment: Black Woman as Text. Russell House. Apr. 25, 1988. Colloquium. Center Colloquium Room. Apr. 26, 1988.
    - Wesleyan University Center for Humanities. Emmet Flood, Mellon Fellow: Some Uses of Narrative in the History of Philosophy: Synoptic Judgment and Philosophical Plot. Russell House. Apr. 18, 1988. Colloquium. Center Colloquium Room. Apr. 26, 1988.
    - Wesleyan University and the Family Service Association of Central CT, Meriden. A Time for Healing: A Symposium on Veterans, America and the Viet Nam War. 107 Shanklin. May 5, 1988.
    - John Martin. Welcome to Harbour Island and Other Sketches. Ezra and Cecile Zilkha Gallery. May 10 - June 2, 1988. Reception. May 10, 1988.
    - Senior Shows, Zilkha Gallery. March 30-April 24, 1988.
- Posters, 1950-
  - 1970s Posters (Drawer 4, Folder 1)
    - Asian Awareness Month, Wesleyan University: From Flux to Focus: Finding Asian America. April 1997.
    - Ujamaa, Spring 79. Calendar of Events. Feb 9, 1979 - Apr 26, 1979.
    - Strike, with clenched fist, screenprinted poster, May 4, 1970. 2 versions.
    - They Ran Out of Teargas: Jeffery Miller, Allison Krause, Sandy Scheuer, William Schneider, May 6, 1970.
    - He is, and He is here…the signs are all around us, May 1970. Small Poster.
    - Frontiers=Repression, May 1970.
    - Image of the barrel of a loaded gun, May 1970, screenprinted poster.
    - The Universe Expects Every Man To Do His Duty In His Parallel Of Latitude -H.D. Thoreau, May 1970.
    - Unity, Connecticut state outline with clenched fist, May 1970. 2 copies, plus one variant printing.
    - Rally to Washington D.C. for the Impeachment of President Nixon, Feb 5. Impeachment Teach-in, Feb 4.
    - Employees of Wesleyan University on Strike (recto), Students Support the Strike (verso). 1978.
    - Employees of Wesleyan University on Strike (recto), Alumni Behind the SECS (verso). 1978.
  - Events Posters, 1970s-1990s (Folder 2)
    - The Archer on the Franks Casket: the Survival of Homeric Myth in Early Medieval England. Amy Vandersall. Davison Art center. March 1, 1973.
    - New Sounds. Seth Dellinger's Vocal Ensemble. The Middletown Creative Orchestra. The Middletown 3. MPR campus center. Sept. 10, year unknown.
    - The Einstein Years. Cultural History and Public Affairs. Sponsored by the Wesleyan University PAC with support from the Connecticut Humanities Council. Science Center. Oct. 15-26 1979.
    - Chaos and Community. Symposium on the occasion of the Wesleyan University Presidential Inauguration. September 22, 1989.
    - An Entertainment for a Tudor Rose. Presented by Ye Knight's Revelers. An evening of Elizabethan Entertainment, Psi U, Nov. 16, 1972.
    - Have a fixation on a Pope-Toledo? Wesleyan University Library, 1971
    - Fifth Annual Woodrow Wilson Debate Society International Debate. Scottish National Debate team vs. Wesleyan Debate Team. CFA Cinema, April 12, ca. 1978.
    - Olla Podrida Yearbook. Reserve a year of your history. Fall 1976.
    - Wes Press Prized. 18 Years of Awards and Honors. Drawing and cutouts on paper, 1976.
    - Fourth Annual Woodrow Wilson Debate Society International Debate. Soviet Union Debate team vs. Wesleyan Debate Team. Cinema. 150 Science Center. March 30, ca. 1975.
    - Find Something. Find out about Wesleyan Fraternities. 1971.
    - Party. Stop Aid-Peek. Special. Student power not Input. South college, CFA and Cage. May 1, year unknown. Benefit for student center.
    - Beaux Arts Ball. Sponsored by the Friends of the Davison Art Center and The Faculty Club for the Benefit of the Davison Print Collection. At Davison Art Center. May 20, 1967. 4 Copies: (1) pink poster, (2) Yellow poster, (1) Yellow poster mounted on green poster board.
    - Ecumenical Celebration. Bring a poem, or something. Share and wear your glad rags. Wesleyan Chapel. Oct. 3, 1971.
    - Transfer. A happening (for Christo). By Allan Kaprow. COL lounge. Feb. 18, 1968.
    - Ecumenical Service. Sermon given by James Helfer of the Religion department. Jun. 6, 1971.
    - Candlelight Concert, December 13, ca. 1960s
    - Candlelight Concert, Wesleyan Concert Choir and Schola Cantorum, CFA, Dec. 16, 1973.
    - Jim Cowdery, Maggie Holtzberg, Dean Kuth, and Jim Martin. How to Change a Flat Tire. Traditional jigs, reels, airs and songs from the British Isles, particularly Ireland and Shetland. Crowell. February 12, 1980.
    - A concert in celebration of 20 years of Coeducation. Featuring: The Yellow Wallpaper, a chamber opera composed by Miriam Gerberg with libretto by Judy McGuire, the Wesleyan Cardinal Sinners and Spirits, Cherly Spencer, and the Wesleyan World Ensemble. October 20, 1991? (+ duplicate).
    - Senior Shows. Senior Art Majors exhibitions. CFA and Davison Art Center Galleries. April 6- May 9 1982.
  - Events Posters, 1960s-1970s (Folder 3)
    - Wesleyan University Admissions, 1967.
    - An Evening of Movies. The Marx Brothers double feature; A Night at the Opera and Duck Soup. Commentary by Professor Joseph W. Reed. At Beta Theta Pi, April 1, 1970.
    - Russell T. Limbach, A Sabbatical Report in the Form of Drawings in Color from Tepoztlan and Rubbings from Monte Alban. At Davison Art Center. November 1961.
    - Wilbert C. Snow. Poetry reading. DKE, Nov. 6, year unknown.
    - Wesleyan University Press A to Z, undated
    - Wesleyan Singers. A musical tribute to Joseph Daltry. With guest artists the Wesleyan Spirits. Crowell Concert Hall. April 20, no year.
    - Stravinsky; CBAIIbbA. Wheaton College and Wesleyan University. At the Memorial Chapel. April 20, no year.
    - Merce Cunningham Festival. Film: Points in Space. Lecture: Merce Cunningham with Elliot Caplan. CFA Theater. October 24, 26, November 2, no year. Poster, wax paper? (Duplicate)
    - Aphorism. A Bad Magazine for Bad Times. Advertisement.
    - EVITA. CFA Theater. November 8-11, no year.
    - A Premiere presentation of 3 films by Wesleyan filmmakers. Beyond the Wizard of Oz, The Ruthyn Curse, and Awakening. Presented by the Wesleyan Film Program. 150 Science Tower. Feb 14, 1973.
    - Wesleyan Student Films. CFA Cinema. May 11-13, no year.
    - Erich Heller. Man guilty: Reflections on Kafka's The Trial. Sponsored by the department of Germon and the Cenger for the Humanities. 184 Science tower (faculty lounge). May 2, 1973.
    - The Archer on the Franks Casket: the Survival of Homeric Myth in Early Medieval England. Amy Vandersall. Davison Art center. March 1 1973.
    - Kasimir Malevich: the Avant Garde and the Russian Revolution. Alan C. Birnholz, Lecturer. Room 100 Davison. Feb 15 1973.
    - Kenneth Burke. Imitation and Style. CFH. Russell House. November 6, 1972.
    - Richard Vann. Periods in Women's History. Russell House. September 24, 1974.
    - Jonathan Guest '74. Anals* of French Renaissance Humanism. Russell House. November 12 1974. Small poster. *with note explaining spelling error.
    - Wesleyan Student Poets. Stephen Alter, Bonnie Bernstein, Dean Holmes, Jerry McGuire, Ruth Pachman. Honors College. Oct 8 1975.
    - Lucille Clifton, reading from her poetry. Poetry at the Honors College and the African American Institute. Russell House. Nov 14 1974.
    - Thom Gunn. Poetry at the Honors college. Russell House. April 19, 1973.
    - Wesleyan Student Poets. Tim Bahti, Kate Ballen, Michel de Konkoly Thege, John Martone, Cedric Noble, Caroline Sutton. Russell House. March 7, 1973.
    - Four Connecticut State poets. Rike Lesser, Frank Levering, Shelley Strohm, Chase Twichell. Honors college, Russell House. Feb 8, 1973.
    - Wilbert Snow. Poetry at the Honors college. Russell House. Dec 6, 1972.
    - Spring Poetry Festival at Wesleyan. April 6-May 14. Year unknown.
    - Three lectures in honor of Paul Horgan, Author in residence, Professor of English Emeritus. November 9, 16, 30, year unknown, 4 copies.
    - The Wesleyan Poetry Program. 20th anniversary Fall 1979.
    - Films by Wesleyan Filmmakers. Shanklin 02. May 15, 1968.
    - General Malaise. Wasn't He Involved in the Dreyfus Case? 150 Science Center. May 12, 1971. Magic Marker on Poster paper.
    - Selamatan. Javanese Gamelan Classical dancers: Hardjo and Jusy Susilo; Indonesian Buffet. McConaughy Hall. Feb 26, 1967.
    - Nikolais Dance Theatre. 1973.
    - Elia Kazan. A retrospective. Presented by the Wesleyan Film Program for the inauguration of the cinema of the CFA. September 1973, 4 copies.
    - Original Art. Earnie D. Kollar. Watercolor on Cardboard.
    - Cosi Fan Tutte. A Theatre/music department production in dedication of the Walter A. Crowell Concert Hall. CFA. October 26-27, 1973.
    - Alex Katz. Davison Art Center. March 9 - April 21, 1974.
    - Edward S. Curtis. The North American Indians. Davison. Aug 29- Sept 29, 1974.
    - Images of Death. Davison Art Center. January 25-March 2, 1975.
    - Recent American Etching. Organized by Wesleyan University for the Office of Exhibitions Abroad, National Collection of Fine Arts, Smithsonian Institution. Davison Arts Center. Oct 10-Nov 23, 1975.
    - Portraits in Prints. Davison Arts Center, February 24-March 10, 1978.
    - A History of Roman Calligraphy. An Exhibition by Robert T. Hoshibata. Olin Library. May 16 - June 1, 1973.
    - George W. Davison, Book Collector, Benefactor. Nov 15 - Dec 31. Year unknown.
    - Poetry at the Honors College. Richard Howard. Russell House. Nov 9, 1972.
    - Russell T. Limbach, "A Sabbatical Report in the Form of Drawings in Color from Tepoztlan and Rubbings from Monte Alban. " At Davison Art Center. November 1961.
    - An Exhibition of work from: The Basic Research Unit Summer Workshop 1965. An Experimental Foundation Workshop. Both Workshops Conducted by Peter Gee. Davison Art Center. Oct 1 - 22, 1966.
    - Animated Flicks. Second Stage. October 9-10, ca. 1970s
  - 1990s- (Folder 4)
    - The Honorable Contance Baker Motley. Homecoming/Family Weekend, Dwight L. Greene Sixth Annual Symposium. Sponsored by the Wesleyan Black Alumni Council. Memorial Chapel. Oct. 24, 1998.
    - President Bennet and the Board of Trustees invite you to welcome the Class of 2002 at Convocation 1998. North College Lawn. Sept 11, 1998.
    - Changing Faces. A History of Wesleyan's Commitment to Racial Diversity. An installation of photographs, materials, and text generated and collected by the Wesleyan University Pluralism and Unity Project, 1995-1997. Center for African American Studies May 30 - June 2, 1999.